which is all about pirate ships and
the idea of there being a pirate
ship on the horizon and the crew of
a boat ignoring the pirate ship on
the horizon. So what I wanted was a
skull and crossbones, but what I got
was a skull.
So there's a couple of points here.
Should I have made a huge fuss
about this? Should it have been a
sticking point? I don't think it
should. I think like once you get to a
certain point when you're publishing
a book, then pick up my cards again
once you've got to a certain point
when you're publishing a book you
lose control you don't have complete
control over it and you could throw
a complete paddy about that but
that's probably not a smart idea to do
that
and you certainly shouldn't get stuck
on it so I spent a month arguing
about my contract and the only
thing that I managed to change as a
result of that argument is the format
of the date and the signature from
the American format to the UK format,
which is not that big a victory,
if truth be told.